Finding Aid for the Yuji Ichioka Papers LSC.0242
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Subject Files
  - Miscellanies
    - 50th Anniversary of the attack on Pearl Harbor, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - 50th Anniversary of the attack on Pearl Harbor, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - 50th Anniversary of the end of the Pacific War and Japan's war responsibilities, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - 50th Anniversary of Japanese American internment, UCLA special commemorations, 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Jordan Hiratsuka file, 1988 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - "Hojishi no Tomoshibi," Chugoku Shimbun, May 10-June 29, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Yuji Ichioka interview with Shimbun Akahata, December 11, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Ishikawa Yoshimi file (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Issei miscellaneous materials (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Japanese American Citizens League campaign for Pardon for Iva Toguri, 1975- 1976 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - "Japanese American Families" project file, 1980-1981 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Japanese American National Museum file, 1986-1988 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Japanese American National Museum file, 1988-1990 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Japanese American National Museum file: pamphlets and newsletters (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Newspaper Research Project, 1982-1986 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Japanese Newspaper Research Project publications, 1984-1986 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Japanese Newspaper Research Project publications, 1984-1986 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Kachi Teruko file, 1981-1988 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Kibei writers (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Kodansha International, 1986-1987 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - "Little Tokyo USA" file (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Matsui Shichiro file (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Murakami Yumiko file, 1993-1994 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Nishioka Kazumasa file, 1989-1990 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Kesa Noda file, 1978-1979 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Noguchi file, 1982-1991 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Nosaka Sanzo file, 1991-1995 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - James Oda file (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - James Oda booklets (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Proposition 187, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Railroad Archives, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Black-Japanese relations (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - "The Repeal and Lagacy" November 1993 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Sado Takuhei file, 1997-1998 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Sakata Yasuo file (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Sakata Yasuo file (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Sakata Yasuo file (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Sakata Yasuo file (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Sakata Yasuo file (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Yuji Ichioka's evaluations of San Francisco State University Asian American Studies program, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Yuji Ichioka's evaluations of San Francisco State University Asian American Studies program, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Yuji Ichioka's evaluations of San Francisco State University Asian American Studies program, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Yoshimi Shibata file, 1980s (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Shibusawa Tazuko wedding (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Strangers From a Different Shore controversy, 1990-1991 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Terminal Island newspaper clippings, 1970s-1980s (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - "Through Innocent Eyes" anthology project, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Togami Soken file, 1980s (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - University of Tokyo visiting professorship, 1999-2000 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Yamaguchi Kosaku file, 1970s-1990s (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Yamato Colony (Florida) newsletters (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - VI Convencion Panamerica Nikkei, Paraguay, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Embassy hostage crisis, Lima, Peru, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Lily Tani Abiko Funeral., 2001 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Tomás Almaguer dissertation chapter draft., 1978 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Eiichiro Azuma file., Undated. (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Ai-li S. Chin, "'Yellow Identity'—'Yellow Power?,'" essay draft, May 1. 1969 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Copyright document relating to "Aliens Ineligible to Citizenship: A History of Japanese Immigrants in the United States, 1885-1924.", Undated. (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Loni Ding's film project on Nisei soldiers in the 442nd Regimental Combat Team and the Military Intelligence Service, including an NEH grant application., 1982 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Arif Dirlik file., 1990s (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Josie Fowler's dissertation prospectus., undated (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Lane Ryo Hirabayashi file., 2002 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - I. F. Stone's Weekly., February 1968-December 1971 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Howard Imazeki file., 1994 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Materials relating to the Institute for Japanese-American Literature ????????????., 1982-1984 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Ito Kazuo ????, "Kashû dokyumentari: Amerika dendenmushi" ???????????:?????????? [California documentaries: American snails]. Nichibei Jiji ??????., November 1987-May 1988 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Materials relating to the Japanese Association for Migration Studies ??????., 1991-1998 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Materials relating to the Japanese Association for Migration Studies ??????., 1991-1998 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Materials relating to Japan's security policies and the U.S.-Japan Security Pact., 1970s-1980s (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Sporadic issues of Nihon Josei Kenkyûkai News ?????????????., 1980-1982 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clipping relating to Japanese women and feminist movement., early 1980s (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Japanese-language publications relating to Japanese women and feminist movement., 1978-1982 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Japanese-language publications relating to Japanese women and feminist movement., 1978-1982 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Materials and miscellaneous notes relating to Japanese women and feminist movement., early 1980s (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Materials relating to Koreans in America., Undated. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Him Mark Lai writings pertaining to Angel Island and early Chinese immigrants., 1976, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Bill Lann Lee file relating to his appointment as the Assistant Attorney General, Civil Rights Division, United States Department of Justice., 1997 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Masao Miyoshi file., Undated. (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous photos and essays., 1980s-1990s (Box 158, Folder 8)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Six 8 inch floppy disks; one 3.5 inch floppy disk.
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Newspaper clippings on Japanese Emperor., 1989 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings on Redress Bill., 1988 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings relating to U.S. politics, civil rights, and Asian American communities., Mostly 1980s-1990s (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Nihon Rikkôkai ????? file., 1989, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Publications by Midori Nishi., 1960s (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Materials pertaining to Okinawa Reversion Treaty., 1969-1971. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Publications relating to Africans and African Americans., 1960s-1970s (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Publications relating to Africans and African Americans., 1960s-1970s (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Publications relating to Asia and Japan., 1960s-1990s (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Publications relating to Asia and Japan., 1960s-1990s (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Publications relating to Asian America; sporadic issues of Rikka and Eastwind., 1981-1984 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Publications relating to Asian America., 1999-2000 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Publications relating to civil rights, labor, race and gender relations., 1960s-1990s (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Other publications., Undated. (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Sakata Yasuo ???? file, including drafts of his dissertation prospectus., ca. 1972 (Box 160, Folder 6)
      (See also Boxes 120-121.)
    - Cedrick M. Shimo file., 1999 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Sonia Shinn Sunoo, "Korea Kaleidoscope: Oral Histories, Vol, One: Early Korean Pioneers in U.S.A, 1903- 1905.", 1982 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Dana Takagi, "Salvaging Class: The Nisei Experience," draft paper., 1990 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Materials relating to Ichioka's visiting professorship at the University of Tokyo., 1999-2000 (Box 161, Folder 4)
      (See also Box 122, Folder 5.)
    - Ellen Wu's thesis draft., Undated. (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Chris Yamada file., 2000 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Kariann A. Yokota's thesis proposal., Undated. (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Karl G. Yoneda file., 1970 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Karl G. Yoneda memorial photos. Sawtelle Japanese Institute., June 26, 1999 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Ayanna Sumiko Yonemura, "Dillon S. Myer and the War Relocation Authority Resettlement of Japanese Americans: A Racialized Planning Project." UCLA dissertation., 2001 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Yoneyama Hiroshi ??? dissertation prospectus., 1992 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Soko Bukai v. YWCA of San Francisco
    - Correspondence between Yuji Ichioka and Dale Tamaki, September 1998-May 2002 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Historical evidence collected by Yuji Ichioka and others (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Legal documents (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Legal documents (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - "Mediation Brief" (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - "Historical Documents for Experts," August 2001 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Soko Bukai v. YWCA of San Francisco (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Materials pertaining to Soko Bukai v. Young Women's Christian Association of San Francisco., 1999-2001 (Box 161, Folder 12)
      (See also Boxes 112-113.)
  - Trip to Peru and Brazil
    - Papers relating to Colegio Cooperativo La Union, Lima (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Papers relating to Japanese Peruvians (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous papers relating to Ichioka's trip to Peru (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Papers relating to Japanese Brazilian communities in Acema and Sao Paulo (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous papers relating to Brazil (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Souvenir medals from Brazil (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Photographs and postcards (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Conference Planning and Proposals
    - Materials relating to the planning of "Nikkei Literature: An International Conference on Nisei and Kibei Writers.", 1990-1991 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Materials relating to the planning of "Comparative Historical Research Project of North and South American Nikkei.", 1993 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and networking pertaining to "Comparative Historical Research Project of North and South American Nikkei.", 1993-1997 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Emi Kasamatsu., 1997-1998 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Conference Presentations and Lectures
    - "Our Worst Wartime Mistake: A Post-Redress Look at the Wartime Internment of Japanese-Americans." Reed College, OR., February 1994 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - "The Backfiring of a Strategy: Michael Woo's 1993 Los Angeles Mayoral Campaign and the Politics of Personal Attacks." Duke University., April 1995 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - "Japanese Americans in Los Angeles: Forging a Community." (Only a conference program) Conference on Mexicans in a Multi-Ethnic Los Angeles., October 2000 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Trips
    - Trips to Japan. University of Tsukuba research project and invited lectures., 1992-2000 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco community lecture trip. "Origins of Japanese Immigration to America.", November 1991 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Salt Lake City research trip., December 1991 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco trip to attend a "Golden Lands, Working Hands" scholars meeting organized by the California Federation of Teachers., December 1992 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Brazil trip for research and networking., April-May 1993 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      (See also Box 156, Folders 1-3.)
    - Peru trip for research and networking., 1995 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Washington DC research trips., 1995, 2000 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Trips to Seattle and Vancouver, Canada., October 1998 (Box 162, Folder 7)
- Periodicals
  - Gardena no Tomo
    - August, December 1941; June-December 1956 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - 1957 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - 1958 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - 1959 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - 1960 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - 1961 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - 1962 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - 1963 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - 1964 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - 1965 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - 1966 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - 1967 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - 1969 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - 1970 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - 1971 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - 1972 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - 1973 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - 1974 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - 1975 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - 1976 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - 1977 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - 1978 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - 1982 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Godaishu
    - March-December 1984 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - 1992-May 1993 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - June 1993-1994 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - 1997-February 1998 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - March 1998-July 1999 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - August 1999-2000 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Hokubei News
    - April-July 1987 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Ikusanga
    - November-June 1987; June-July 1988 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Japanese American Review
    - 1939 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - 1940 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - 1941 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Literary Journals
    - Reimei, 1931-1932 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Bandwagon, 1950; Gyo-Sho, ca. 1930s; Ascension, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Kamani, 1924, ca. 1960 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Mohave, 1943-1944; Kushu Sekirei, 1945 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Nippon to Amerika
    - 1935 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - 1937 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - January-February, April 1938 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - September-October 1938; February 1941 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Nisei Vue & Scene
    - Nisei Vue, 1948; Scene 1950, 1951 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - NJAHS Newsletter
    - 1987-1989 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - NY Bungei
    - 1955-1957 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - 1963, 1965, 1968, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Poston Bungei
    - 1943 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - 1944 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - January-May 1945 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - June-September 1945 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Scene
    - 1952 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - March-July 1953 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - August, October 1953; 1954 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - 1955 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Senryu Tsubame
    - 1962 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - 1963 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - 1964 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - 1966, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Shogyo Jiho
    - January-April 1938 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - May-June 1938; November 1939; January-February 1940 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - April-September 1940 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - 1941 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Personal File
  - UCLA Undergraduate Study
    - Ichioka UCLA Class Notes: Mandarin, Logic, and Philosophy., 1961-1962 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Ichioka UCLA History Class Term Papers., Spring 1961-Spring 1962. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - UC Berkeley Graduate Study
    - Ichioka East Asian Studies Graduate Seminar Paper: "Takayama Chogyu and His Nihon Shugi: Its Nature and Significance.", ca. 1968 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Research Materials relating to Takayama ChÔgyû., ca. 1967-1968 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Ichioka's Review of Joseph R. Leverson, Confucian China and Its Modern Fate (Berkeley, 1965)., 1968 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Shotaro F. Hayashigatani, "The Reversion of Okinawa Islands: A Critical Analysis of U.S. Control.", 1970 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Papers presented at the colloquia and symposia organized by the Center for Japanese and Korean Studies., 1968, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Papers presented at the colloquia and symposia organized by the Center for Japanese and Korean Studies., 1971 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Papers presented at the colloquia and symposia organized by the Center for Japanese and Korean Studies., 1972 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Papers presented at the colloquia and symposia organized by the Center for Japanese and Korean Studies., 1973 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Miscellanies
    - Ichioka Harvard University Graduate School Application: "Statement of Goals and Backgrounds.", 1972 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper articles relating to Ichioka's life, politics and work., Undated. (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper articles relating to Ichioka's life, politics and work., Undated. (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Professional expenses and receipts., 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Materials relating to Ichioka's passing: memorials, tributes and obituaries., Undated. (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Materials relating to Ichioka's passing: memorials, tributes and obituaries., Undated. (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Materials relating to Ichioka's passing: Amerasia Journal special issue 28:3 (2002)., Undated. (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Asian American Studies and Movement
  - UCLA Asian American Studies Center
    - Proposals for UCLA Asian American Studies Center, and materials relating to its early operation., 1969-1971 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Asian American student activism in support of an Asian American Studies program., 1969 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Materials relating to CED 103: "Orientals in America.", Spring 1969 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - CED 103: "Orientals in America." Lecture notes., Undated. (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Student papers for CED 103: "Orientals in America" (June 1969) and History 198: "History of the Asians in America" (Spring 1970)., Undated. (Box 143, Folder 1)
      (See also Box 104, Folder 7.)
    - Materials relating to CED 106: "A History of Japanese Americans.", Spring 1972, Fall 1975 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      (See also Box 104, Folder 8.)
    - Proposals of courses taught by Linda P. Shin, Franklin Odo, Alan T. Nishio, Lillian Yeh, and Joe Grant Masaoka., 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Ichioka curriculum vita, employment form and research report., 1969-1976 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - KCOP TV Channel 13 special program on UCLA Asian American Studies Center., October 1969 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Ichioka Research Proposal., 1974 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Faculty appointment, promotion, and other personnel matters, including Ichioka's curriculum vita., 1979-1985 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Faculty appointment, promotion, and other personnel matters, including Ichioka's history adjunct professorship., 1986-1988 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Faculty appointment, promotion, and other personnel matters, including Ichioka's 1994 application for a History faculty position., 1989-1991, 1994, 1996-1997, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous documents pertaining to Ichioka's work as an Asian American Studies faculty at UCLA., Undated. (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Research materials compiled by the UCLA Asian American Studies Center., 1971-1976 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Various publications and pamphlets by the UCLA Asian American Studies Center., 1969-1972 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Asian American Studies on Other Campuses
    - Papers relating to UC Berkeley Asian ?American? Studies., 1969-1972 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley Asian ?American? Studies Conference., September 1969 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - UC Berkeley Asian ?American? Studies Courses., 1969-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Studies programs and student organizations at California State College, Dominguez Hills, San Jose State University, UC Irvine, and Pennsylvania State University., ca. 1970-1971 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Early Asian American Community Activism
    - Asian-American Ad-Hoc Committee on Hiroshima and Nagasaki (San Francisco)., ca. 1970 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Asian Americans for Action (New York)., ca. 1969 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Asian Americans for Peace (Los Angeles), including Asian Americans Against the Crime of Silence., 1969-1970 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Asian Americans for Peace (Los Angeles), including Asian Americans Against the Crime of Silence., 1969-1970 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Asian Americans Unite!, no. 2 (1970)., Undated. (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Asian News Service: News & Events, 1:1 (Nov. 16, 1970)., Undated. (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Asian People's Newsletter, no. 4-7, September-December 1970, January 1971 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Papers relating to San Francisco Chinatown community organizations., ca. late 1960s-1970s (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Materials relating to the Chinatown-North Beach Community English Language Center., ca. 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Japanese American Citizens League (JACL) Liberation Campaign., ca. 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - JACL Bay Area Community Chapter., 1971-1973 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - JACL International Relations Committee., 1971-1973 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Community Pioneer Center (Los Angeles)., 1969-1971 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Materials relating to other Japanese American community organizations., Undated. (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Oriental Service Center and the Council of Oriental Organizations (Los Angeles)., 1969-1970 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Bay Area Asian American community organizations and political activism., ca. 1969-1971 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Papers relating to the Title II Repeal Campaign., 1974 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous materials pertaining to radical/revolutionary politics., Late 1960s-1970s (Box 145, Folder 8)
- Card Catalog
  - Annotated card catalog of source materials relating to the histories of China, Japan, and Japanese America., ca. 1970s (Box 162, Folder 8-9)